http://www.musicmotion.com/info/privacy-policy.asp

Kodaly & Orff
Movement (Books and Audio)
Metronomes & Tuners
Music Stands, Lights, Etc.
Ethnic & Folk, Whistles
Handbells, Tone Chimes, Etc.
Writing Aids
Search:
in
Search All (Quick)All FieldsNameDescriptionPart # (Contains)Part # (Starts With)
Our Privacy and Security Promise
Music in Motion, in business since 1976, values your personal security
and privacy, and has established this Privacy Policy so that you can
understand the care with which we treat your Personal Information.
Because this Privacy Policy applies to any person who provides
information to Music in Motion, we strongly urge you to review this
Privacy Policy in its entirety.
What customer Information  does Music in Motion retain?
You can browse Music in Motion’s website without providing us with any personal information.
When you create an account or place an order, we request only the information necessary to complete these actions.
To create an account: name, user name, password, email address
To place an order: billing and shipping address(es), payment information, phone number
Does Music in Motion share the information it receives?
We will never sell, rent or share your personal information with a 3rd party, unless required by law. We care deeply about protecting your privacy.
How secure is customer information?
The personal information you send to Music in Motion to place orders or
register for special services such as our newsletter, is securely
protected.
We maintain up-to-date Internet security technology to
prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of all customer information. All
credit card data is encrypted when orders are entered and when
transmitted for processing.
It is important that you protect against
unauthorized access to your password and to your computer.
Please be
sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.
How does Music in Motion use customer information?
We use customer information through our website to enhance the experience of visitors to our site.
To furnish you with fast, accurate delivery of products you order.
To email confirmation of your order and ship date, or contact you about your order if necessary.
To provide you with periodical email updates on new products, special offers, and discount coupons, only if you choose to opt-in. We will never spam you.
To improve the content, navigation, and search functions of our website.
To prevent and detect fraud, infringement, and other potential misuse of our website.
To send you the Music in Motion printed color catalog filled with our
carefully selected music education resources and gifts (mailed twice
annually).
You may opt-out of receiving email offers and product updates in Your Account
under “E-newsletter and E-mail Subscription Options.”
If you wish to
be removed from the Music in Motion catalog mailing list, email your
request to unsubscribe@musicmotion.com, call 1 800 807-3520 with your opt-out request, or mail your request to: Music in Motion, Attn: Remove From Mailing List, PO Box 869231, Plano, TX
75086-9231.
Please include your name and the mailing address you would like us to remove from our mailing list in your opt-out request.
Music in Motion cares about the environment.
If you are receiving
duplicate copies of the Music in Motion catalog, please send us your
name, mailing address, and 5-character Keycode on the back of your
catalog or on the envelope.
Email this information to unsubscribe@musicmotion.com, mail it to the address above, or fax it to 1 866 943-8906.
What about Cookies?
A cookie is an alphanumeric identifier that is transferred through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. A cookie does not collect or keep your name or other personally identifiable information. Cookies provide you with the following conveniences:
storage of items in your Shopping Cart and Wishlist between visits
Multimedia features on our website, including video, audio, and special interactive features
If you do not wish to take advantage of these features, please refer to your web browser's Help section for instruction on how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have your browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, because cookies allow you to take advantage of some valuable features of musicmotion.com, we recommend that you leave them turned on.
What about links to other websites?
Musicmotion.com contains links
to other websites that we believe you might find useful and informative.
Music in Motion is not responsible for the privacy practices or the
content of these other sites.
We encourage you to independently review
the privacy policies of each site you visit.
Policy Modifications
We reserve the right to amend this Privacy Policy from time to time, but we will always maintain your personal security and privacy, and will never rent, sell or share your information
with 3rd parties.
We will post any changes here, so please check back
periodically.
Your continued use of our website after any change has
been posted constitutes acceptance of the change to this Privacy Policy.
Questions about our Privacy Policy?
Please send any questions and/or comments you may have to customerservice@musicmotion.com.
Resources
Free Catalog
Sign-up for Emails
Our Blog
- Tips for Music Teachers
- Prevent Hearing Loss
- Musical Birthdays
Teacher's Guides
FAQ
Share ideas with other music educators & follow us for exclusive specials
© 2012 Music In Motion | P.O. Box 869231 | Plano, Texas 75086-9231 | Phone 972.943.8744 | Toll Free 1.800.807.3520 | Fax 972.943.8906 | Customer Service
